[
	{
		"question": "1 x 1",
		"answer": "1",
	},
	{
		"question": "1 x 2",
		"answer": "2",
	},
	{
		"question": "1 x 3",
		"answer": "3",
	},
	{
		"question": "1 x 4",
		"answer" : "4",
	},
	{
		"question": "1 x 5",
		"answer": "5",
	},
	{
		"question": "1 x 6",
		"answer": "6",
	},
	{
		"question": "1 x 7",
		"answer": "7",
	},
	{
		"question": "1 x 8",
		"answer" : "8",
	},
	{
		"question": "1 x 9",
		"answer": "9",
	},
	{
		"question": "1 x 10",
		"answer": "10",
	},
	{
		"question": "1 x 11",
		"answer": "11",
	},
	{
		"question": "1 x 12",
		"answer" : "12",
	},
]